when the heat is on there's no pulling
punches you can't just sit there and
take it you have to get up and get
moving so you have the tightest rebuttal
and have the strength to carry a stage
full of tired celebrity I'm treading for
a roast not America's next top auto
mechanic you two idiots look like you
skip leg day and graduation day if
you're out for roast blood you need to
cross some lines these two couldn't
train a dog to lick itself you gotta
build thick skin if you're gonna trade
jobs with the other Roasters come on and
remember if the jokes stink make sure
you don't degree it won't let you down
it's time for the gloves to come off you
guys help